listz.in 2015-03-15

# Privacy Policy - Listz

This privacy policy sets out how “Listz.in” uses and protects any information that you give us while using it.

Listz.in is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Listz.in may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 01/01/2015.

**What we collect**

We may collect the following information:

  * Name & Website
  * contact information including email address

**When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you commenting or enter information on our site.

**What we do with the information we gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * To improve our website in order to better serve you.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new posts which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
